http://www.municipalcourt.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy of Law Office of Ronald P. Mondello, New Jersey |
General Information
Common Circumstances Associated with DUI/DWI charges in New Jersey
The New Jersey Motor Vehicle Commission Cannot Suspend Your License For a Pending DWI Charge
DUI/DWI Cases Due To Drugs in New Jersey
Case History And Contact Information
Useful Tips
What To Do After Being Charged With A DUI/DWI in New Jersey?
Common Mistakes Committed by People Charged with DUI/DWI In New Jersey.
Hiring An Attorney
What to look for When Hiring an Attorney to Represent your Case?
Is Retaining a Public Defender a Viable Option?
Driving While Your License Is under Suspension
Moving Violations and The Interstate Driver’s License Compact
Underage Drivers and Traffic Infractions
Leaving the Scene of an Accident
New Jersey’s Unsafe Driving Statute
General Info About Traffic Offenses
What Are the Most Common Traffic Tickets Issued in New Jersey?
Commercial Drivers (CDL Holders) Are Subject to an Enhanced Point System
Do You Have to Appear in Court for a Moving Violation?
A DWI Charge Is the Most Serious of Vehicle-Related Offenses
Is a DWI a Criminal Charge in New Jersey?
Useful Tips for Traffic Offense Cases
It Is Advisable to Retain an Attorney before the Penalties for Driving While Suspended Begin to Compound
Common Misconceptions about Moving Violations
Criminal Defense
Shoplifting Offenses
What is shoplifting offense?
What to do if I am accused of shoplifting by a Store Security Guard?
Should I hire an Attorney and what can an Attorney do for me?
Are some shoplifting offenses more serious than others?
Frequently Asked Questions
Charged with a DWI?
(Useful Info Revealed that may
help
you Navigate your DWI Case)
Fight Your Traffic Ticket
(Useful Info Revealed to Fight Your Traffic Ticket)
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
By
Ronald P. Mondello
Related Articles
Terms of Use
Client Testimonials
Contact Us
Frequently Asked Questions
Home
© 2013 Ronald P. Mondello, Esq. All Rights Reserved.
